More...
More.
Give me more!
The Have-Nots
Somebody! Help!
Come on, come on, come on!
Warriors? I-I'm saved...
We'll take it from here!
If you see one goblin,
there's a hundred more around!
Don't let a single one escape!
Yeah!
I'm starving...
I finally hit Level 6
after today's goblin hunt!
Well, there were a lot of them.
And we made off with quite a haul.
Let's cash out and then split the take.
Oh, yeah!
Goblin hunting, huh?
That'll never be me.
I'm useless, with a stomach that
never stops growling, to boot.
All thanks to this worthless skill...
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony
[Gluttony]
Guess I should be grateful
to even have a job.
Oh, thanks for coming!
The holy knights are coming through...
It's that trio of Vlerick siblings.
I'm so terribly sorry,
Sir Hado, let me just—
What do you think you're doing
to my boots, you wretch?
I didn't mean to...
You're talking back? To me?
You must know what happens
if you insult holy knights, right?
Your head comes off.
I'm so terribly sorry!
Hado, Memil, that's enough.
Don't let it happen again.
Y-yes, sir!
You got lucky.
Very lucky!
You all right?
That was awful.
Unbelievable. Hard to believe that
Lady Roxy is a holy knight like that lot.
Shift's almost over.
Just gotta make it through.
Hey, Fate.
Have you done a proper job
filling in for us today?
Yes, Sir Rafale.
Is that right? In that case...
That's your pay.
Pick it up.
Yes, sir.
Sorry! You were so filthy,
I didn't notice you.
Absolutely pathetic.
That noisy gut makes it seem
like we don't keep you fed.
You trying to embarrass the Vlerick family?!
In this world, there are haves...
and there are have-nots.
You useless maggot!
What separates them...
Who do you owe your livelihood to, again?
Someone with a worthless skill like yours
is only earning money thanks to
the grace of holy knights like us...
You should be so grateful!
...are the special powers
bestowed by the gods: skills.
When you slack off, it reflects
poorly on us, your employers.
On your feet.
Come on! Get up already.
I believe he needs to be taught a lesson.
Defiant dogs need strict
discipline, after all.
Stop this!
Inflicting that kind of abuse on
the citizens we're sworn to protect...
It is not the act of a holy knight.
Roxy Hart...
Watching the gate is an
honorable duty for a holy knight.
A duty that should be your responsibility.
It is also the duty of holy knights to
provide employment for the have-nots.
You claim kind of treatment is necessary?
This amounts to a difference
in professional opinion, I'd say.
If you'll excuse us. Come along, Hado, Memil.
Fate... are you all right?
Yes.
Rafale...
Stay still, please. You're bleeding.
That's better.
Th-Thank you so much.
We're cohorts when it
comes to watching the gate.
Besides, this is how a holy knight
should conduct themselves.
Now, it's time for me to relieve you.
Oh, right! Thank you so much.
Fate...
If this kind of thing happens again,
please, tell me.
It's okay.
But...
I'm used to it. If you'll excuse me.
Fate...
If this kind of thing happens again,
please, tell me.
I know what Lady Roxy said,
but with how he is,
there's no telling what he might do.
I can't risk getting her involved.
They knock you around again?
If this keeps up... you're gonna
end up like the last guy.
Endless abuse, brutal labor...
There's only one outcome for that,
and it's a nasty one.
Thanks for the meal, barkeep.
I'll be praying you don't end up like that.
Stupid useless Gluttony...
I wish I could've been born
with something worthwhile, too.
I'm not asking to be a holy knight.
I'd take being a warrior, or even
a merchant or a craftsman.
But... there's no changing how things are.
When you have nothing,
you're trapped as a loser.
Thieves?!
I need to let Lady Roxy know!
You're certain?
Yeah! I saw them myself. There's no doubt.
I'll need to apprehend them.
Please, take over here for me.
Right. Good luck, Lady Roxy.
I'll take care of it.
Appearances aside,
I'm quite confident in my skills.
Is it over...?
Lady Roxy trusted me with this.
If I run, it'll cause trouble for her!
I can't let him get away!
He's already injured...
Even I can handle this!
It's over...
Gluttony skill has activated.
Increasing stats.
Skills Identify and Telepathy
have been added.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony
Identify
Telepathy
My Gluttony skill... activated?
What in the world was that?
Fate!
Fate, are you all right? Were you hurt?
He doesn't look well. It's worrying...
Is anything wrong?
That was just like...
I could hear her inner voice.
Uh, no, I'm not hurt.
I see.
What a relief. I'm so glad.
Again?
I need to report this to my superiors.
Do you understand, Fate?
I can't hear it anymore.
Fate? Are you listening?
Oh, right! You can take credit
for all of this, Lady Roxy.
But you slew one yourself, Fate.
If Sir Rafale finds out about it...
It would cause you problems, wouldn't it?
I can't make trouble for her.
I understand, but without you,
I would've failed in my duty.
Please, let me show my gratitude.
Oh, that's not necessary.
Let me think...
She's not listening.
I know!
Would you like to work for the Hart family?
Or do you intend to serve
the Vlericks until it kills you?
Lady Roxy...
You needn't worry about them.
Your future is yours to decide, Fate.
A future where I'm treated
like trash by them...
Or a bright one where
I can work for Lady Roxy...
Still, if I quit, then whoever
replaces me would...
I told you. Defending the gate
is the duty of a holy knight.
Whatever happens, it won't
be your responsibility.
If Lady Roxy thinks so,
then it's probably true.
It'd be my honor, Lady Roxy.
Wonderful!
What's this?
My stats are in the triple digits now...
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony
Identify
Telepathy
How'd that happen?
And what's "Identify"? And "Telepathy"?
He doesn't look well. It's worrying.
Wait, was that Telepathy?
Gluttony has activated.
It actually activated...
and what's going on with my body?
But with stats like this,
I might be able to beat monsters.
Looking for a sword, sir?
Oh, yes.
What kind of budget are you thinking?
Uh, well...
Great, you're poor.
What a waste of hospitality...
You can't buy a weapon with
that kind of chump change.
It's been five years since
I came to the royal capital.
These two silver coins are everything
I've been able to save up by working...
All you'll be able to afford are
those trash weapons in the barrel.
I was curious about this...
Oh, sir!
Well, I guess it's better than nothing.
Identify.
Zero for both durability and strength, huh?
This one, too.
And this...
Filthy, and treated like trash.
A lot like me.
Hey, you.
It talked?!
I'm pretty sure this sword just talked.
"Greed. One-handed sword."
I'll make it worth your while,
so buy me, Gluttony.
How'd you know about that?
We have a lot in common, you and I.
We do?
This one looks good, too.
You have an eye for quality, sir!
Did you hear the rumors, Rafale?
Roxy is apparently trying to
hire Fate for the Hart household
without even asking us!
Let's teach her what happens
when you defy the Vlerick family!
There's no shortage of replacements for Fate.
It's not worth the trouble, Memil.
She was complaining about
our handling of guard duty, too!
The Harts and the Vlericks are part of the
five great families that support the kingdom.
There's no point in
complicating that right now.
It's time I head to
the military district, anyway.
Again?
What part of your studies
has you so enthusiastic?
The study of how to become immortal.
Immortality...?
Oh, Rafale, you don't have to tease me!
"Fate Graphite."
What?
Fate Graphite...
Congratulations, I've learned your name.
Like that's some kind of favor...?
Here they come, Fate.
Gluttony skill has activated.
Increasing stats.
Skill Strength Boost has been added.
It happened again.
Get a load of that.
I guess they were right about "When you see
one goblin, there's a hundred more around."
A-A hundred?!
They're coming!
Dammit!
Gluttony skill has activated.
More new skills...
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony
Identify
Telepathy
Strength
Boost (Low)
Vitality
You're probably filled up now, right?
Now that you mention it... my stomach
hasn't growled even once today.
That's never happened before.
But I thought you were born with
the only skills you'd ever have.
You can thank the Gluttony skill for that.
Normally, your stats increase from battles,
and based on your experience,
your level goes up.
But the Gluttony skill
steals stats and skills,
at the cost of not
benefiting from experience.
That's why I'm still level one, then.
How do you know all this?
Because we're in the same boat.
We are?
Your Gluttony skill isn't the kind of thing
you want other people finding out about.
It's one of the skills that defy divine law.
So, I'd better do my fighting alone.
You've got me, don't you?
Now that you're wielding me,
you're not alone anymore, Fate.
So, you accept me as your master?
Whoa, there, let's not get cocky.
But it's the truth, isn't it?
Pipe down!
Well, I guess I'll head back for today.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Collect those goblin ears.
You need to get paid.
Maybe I shouldn't have killed all of them...
Thirty eight goblins earns me three
silver and eighty bronze coins.
That's enough for meat with dinner!
Hold it. My maintenance comes first.
Do a proper job and treat me
like the gem I am.
For a sword, you've got
a real high opinion of yourself.
I didn't get the name Greed on accident!
Yeah, yeah. Meat comes first.
It's been five years since—
Watch where you're going, you dumbass.
Sorry about that.
Help!
Let's go.
What are his skills...?
Vitality
Strength
Agility
Spirit
Magic
The Conceal skill, huh?
That keeps his skills from being
visible, even against Identify.
So there's no telling what he could do?
Yeah.
What's your call, Fate?
What do you mean?
I can't just ignore this!
You should be happy!
There's a place even worthless trash
like you can serve some purpose.
You're gonna be a toy for the holy knights!
Ain't that great?
Huh?! Huh?!
Hold on. This guy's pretty tough.
This is your last chance to turn back.
I've finally got some kind of power...
You scared?
If someone's suffering in front
of me, I want to help them!
Hunger Boost
"Hunger Boost."